http://www.jborrell.com/index.php/8-static/9-legal-notes

LEGAL NOTICE
JOSÉ BORRELL S.A.  retains all copyrights in any text, graphic images, and software owned  and hereby authorizes you to electronically copy documents published herein solely for the purpose of transmitting or viewing the information. You may not mirror, modify or otherwise alter any files in this website for rebroadcast, or print the information contained therein, without written permission from JOSÉ BORRELL S.A. or  BORRELL USA Corp. Except as expressly provided above, nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring any license or right under any JOSÉ BORRELL S.A. or BORRELL USA Corp copyright, patent or trademark.
BORRELL,BORRELL SMART SORTER and their respective logos as well as corporate and product identity used herein, are trademarks of  JOSÉ BORRELL S.A. and/or BORRELL USA Corp. and may not be used without permission.
Legal Notices
The information in this publication, including text, images, and links, are PROVIDED "AS IS" BY JOSÉ BORRELL S.A. SOLELY AS A CONVENIENCE TO ITS DEALERS AND CUSTOMERS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. JOSE BORRELL S.A.. assumes no responsibility for errors or omissions in this publication or other documents which are referenced by or linked to this publication. This publication could include technical or other inaccuracies, and not all products or services referenced herein are available in all areas. Changes are periodically added to the information, and JOSÉ BORRELL S.A. may change the products or services described in this publication at any time. Contact  JOSÉ BORRELL S.A. for further information before relying on any information contained herein.
Should you choose to respond directly to JOSE BORRELL SA with comments, questions, suggestions, ideas or the like relating to this Web Site or BORRELL  products and services, you agree that such information shall be deemed as non-confidential and  JOSÉ BORRELL S.A. and BORRELL USA shall have no obligation to respond and be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute the information to others without limitation, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing, and marketing products incorporating such information.
José BorrellS.A.incompliance with the provisions of Article10 of spanish Law 34/2002 of 'Services of the Information Society and Electronic Commerce', through its web site provides access,by electronic means,permanently,easy, direct and free, informationon its corporate, tax information,registration, address and communications.Respecto fthe registration information on José Borrell SA, these are detailed below:
C.I.F A-03713 146
Register of Alacant/Alicante, Folio 90, Volume1288,General Section Page A-5864
***
Netscape is a registered trademark and the Netscape Navigator logo is a trademark of Netscape Communications Corporation. Microsoft is a registered trademark and the Internet Explorer is a trademark of Microsoft Corporation. Acrobat and the Acrobat logo are trademarks of Adobe Systems Incorporated. Apple and QuickTime are trademarks of Apple Computer Inc. Nothing contained in these Web pages should be construed as granting or permitting any right to use such trademarks.
WEBSITE PRIVACY STATEMENT
José Borrell S.A. complies with regulations established by spanish Law 15/1999 on Protection of Personal Data, Data Protection Act (LOPD)  and other legislation that develops.
At the outset, it becomes clear that for access to certain information and content, the user must pre register as such, must accept as established in it, according to the LOPD, the treatment of personal data , to be incorporated into our file.
José Borrell S.A. agrees to remove personal data when they are no longer necessary or relevant for the purpose for which it was collected through the form provided for that purpose and to respond to requests for information made by the user, the controller being José Borrell SA
JOSE BORRELL SA and BORRELL USA Corp. are committed to providing customers with the best value products and services in the field and online. We've asked for your personal identity information, so we want you to know how it will be used. By registering with or contacting us through BORRELL family of corporate web sites, you agree that any information or comments you provide may be shared between JOSE BORRELL SA, its affiliated companies and dealers, and used without restriction to process customer orders and improve or market our products and services. We will not sell or rent your information to any third party, and will exercise reasonable efforts to keep the information secure.JOSE BORRELL SA recognizes and respects your online privacy.
Cookies When you visit our websites we may send you a cookie. A cookie stores a small data file on your computer. This file enables us to recognize you each time you visit us. Cookies help us in many ways, for example, by saving your region and language preference and for purposes of collecting non-personal data.
BORRELL's  web security cookies are not used to collect personal information on this web site.
This website’s cookies will either be deleted or not deleted automatically when you close your browser depending upon the need to retain the information in the cookie between your visits to this website.  If you do not allow this website to use cookies, then certain features or sections of the site may not be available to you or may not function as expected.  Cookies can also be removed or blocked by following the help directions in your browser.
Links JOSE BORRELL S.A. Web sites contain links to other Web sites. JOSE BORRELL S.A is not liable for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites.
Forms Individual forms have their own data privacy statements. Please be sure to check these privacy statements before submitting the form.
©2018 JOSE BORRELL SA All Rights Reserved.
Equipment for Almonds, Hazelnuts, Pistachios, Walnuts, other Nuts, Seeds and Legumes
© 2020 JOSÉ BORRELL S.A. & BORRELL USA Corp. -  Legal terms - Terms of Sales
BORRELL ®, BORRELL AUTOMATION ® , BORRELL SMART SORTER ® , TAMING SUN ® , HYPERQUADRO ® , BORRELL BHC HULLER COMBO ® , BORRELL BSSS SMART SHELLING SYSTEM ® y TURBO SORT SCREEN ® are trademarks owned by  JOSE BORRELL S.A. Other service marks, trademarks and trade names referred to on this website are the property of their respective owners.
